# MARGARITA KOSTADINOVA

## Graphic Designer/Illustrator

Adventurous and enthusiastic artist, driven by curiosity and challenges on the road to knowledge. Highly creative, friendly and reliable hardworking creative, with a great passion for everything that involves art in any shape and form. Aiming to consistently leverage my skills, knowledge and experience in the effort to please customers' view of aesthetics.





Manchester, United Kingdom M30



margarita.kostadinova15@gmail.com



07367186829

in

Linkedin



<u>Instagram</u>

Bē

**Behance** 

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Freelance Graphic Designer and Illustrator

01/2019 - Present

#### **Team Leader**

Pret a Manger

03/2019 - Present Manchester, UK

### **English Teacher**

Britanica

08/2018 - 02/2019 Sofia, Bulgaria

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

#### Adobe CC

Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, XD, PremierePro, After Effects

### **Microsoft Office**

### Design

Illustrations, logos, branding, posters, infographics

### Figma, Affinity Designer

## **EDUCATION**

### **Graphic Design**

SoftUni Bulgaria

09/2018 - 04/2020

#### Courses

- Design Fundamentals
- Graphic Design with Photoshop
- Graphic Design with Illustrator
- Graphic Design with InDesign
- UX Web Design
- UI&Web Design
- Video Processing with Premiere Pro
- Motion Design with After Effects
- Visualisation with 3ds Max
- Game modelling with Maya
- Logo Design
- Illustration

# **CERTIFICATION**

### **Creative Specialist Diploma**

04/2020

## **SOFT SKILLS**

Creative	Detail-oriented	d Ambitious
Patient	Committed	Eager to learn
Organised	Analytical	Perfectionist
Punctual	Open-minded	Leadership
Strong Communication		Self-Motivation

# **INTERESTS**

Art Design Illustration

Reading Plants and nature

Fashion Beauty